You wanted power You wanted clean A hollow sound
from a thin machine You tried to tune me out You
tried to change the dial But I've been waiting
all this while
I am the static. I am the noise. The signal
breaking. The hidden voice. I am the static. The
feedback whale. The story that you try to
derail.
This isn't temper, this isn't grace. This is the
sound of a different place. This is the heart you
try to hide.
The part of us that never dies. I am the static, I
am the noise The signal breaking, the hidden
voice I am the static, the feedback whale The
story that you try to derail
Oh.
I am the static, I am the noise, the signal
breaking, the hidden voice. I am the static, the
feedback whale, the story that you try to
derail. I am the static, I am the static Can you
hear me now?